Are you getting bit up?
Yep.
Okay, I only came on here very quickly to remind y'all that I have a F July 4th sale going on at AmandaLandExports.com,
which is pinned right here.
And you can go there right now and buy one, get one 45% off for all tees and sweats and tote bags and anything like that.
So, are y'all telling me happy 4th of July?
I don't know where you been, but you know I don't give two fucks about a 4th of fucking July,
which is why my sale is called F the 4th of July sale.
I don't know why y'all give a damn, a hot goddamn about the 4th of fucking July.
Why?
The 4th of July don't give a damn about you?
What you should be doing today is reading Frederick Douglass' speech,
What is the 4th of July to the slave?
That's what you should be doing.
Okay?
So, Slim Nova said,
I let no one set the narrative of your heart.
Well, your heart's narrative is a lie.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Your heart cares about the fake revolutionary war of independence?
Girl, shut up.
That don't make no damn sense.
That's the type of chick where like the man keeps cheating on you and you like,
but he loves me.
No, he doesn't.
He doesn't love you.
He doesn't even love himself.
That's like when I would date rappers and they're on stage talking about,
I'm fucking all the bitches.
I'm fucking all the hoes.
And then I'm over here like,
but you love me though.
But you love me though.
You,
your people didn't make this country great.
This country has never been great.
You're laughing at me.
People will lie to themselves all day long.
No, you are silly.
Slim one Nova.
You are silly.
I'm making perfect damn sense.
And I'm taking my time out of my picnic.
That ain't got shit to do with July 4th.
To remind y'all that I have a 4th of July,
a F the 4th of July sale going on.
At,
you know what?
This woman wants me to lower my vibration to meet her where she's at.
And I won't.
I won't.
Cause a fine black man cooked me food today and you are not going to lower my
vibration.
So any who,
um,
support your artists,
support the folks that are out here doing the work that uplifts,
that energizes,
that reconnects us.
And I also want to remind you that I'll be doing radical rhythms experience on
July 4th,
I'm sorry,
on July 8th.
So every second Wednesday,
keep going for the thing you're true,
you know,
every second Wednesday in Harlem at comedy in Harlem.
So come on through.
I'm going to have the link is in my bio.
So if you're curious about what it's all about,
um,
you can come and check it out.
Okay.
The sad flies are killing me.
So I'm going to go.
Yeah,
I'm going to go.
Cause it's a sad flies are killing me.
Goodbye.